

Scott Stiritz

SUMMARY

Dependable, friendly, confident, and experienced in the world of Information Technology –
dedicated to achieve the highest quality customer service understanding the importance of
supporting end users time and again. A self-starter that possesses great skill, enthusiasm,
care and leadership ability. Detailed-oriented and self-motivated, with a strong sense of
work ethic.

Core Competencies

- Skilled IT Technician
- Excellent Work Ethics
- New User Training
- Software Troubleshooting
- Multitasking
- Team Oriented Worker
- Excellent Customer Service
- Organizational Skills

EDUCATION

- New Horizons Institute, Orlando, Florida, Microsoft Certified Systems Administrator
- University of Phoenix, Online, Credits Earned
- Palm Beach State College, Lake Worth, Florida, Computer Science, Credits Earned

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

April 2016 – September 2016 Helpdesk Technician Harris Corporation

- Answer phone calls from users, troubleshoot computer issues over the phone
- Document calls using proprietary ticketing system
- Troubleshoot proprietary software and route tickets to the proper groups.
- Active Directory Management (change user account passwords)
- Serve as chat technician

November 2014 - April 2016

District Computer Coordinator

State of Wyoming, Enterprise Technology Services

- Take phone calls from users, troubleshoot computer issues over the phone
- Document calls using proprietary ticketing system
- Directly support Wyoming Highway Patrol; office, mobile, and proprietary equipment
- Work with Headquarters to troubleshoot, install, and maintain network infrastructure



- Order, setup, and install new desktop, laptop, and mini computers
- Active Directory Management (change user account passwords)
- Setup and maintain network and local printers
- Setup and maintain Chromecast A/V Equipment
- Drive to district sites; maintain desktops, laptops, network infrastructure equipment
- Responsible for district computer inventory
- Support Multiple Operating Systems
 - Microsoft Windows 10
 - Microsoft Windows 8.1
 - Microsoft Windows 7
- Support Microsoft Office Suites 2007/2010
 - Word
 - Excel
 - PowerPoint
- Remote Desktop Support
 - Landesk Remote Software
 - TeamViewer Remote Software
- Assist customers with mapping network drives
- Responsible for maintenance of State vehicle

March 2014 – November 2014 Computer Desktop Support

CDI Corporation (Contract)

- Take phone calls from users, troubleshoot computer issues over the phone
- Document calls using proprietary ticketing system
- Remote Desktop Support
 - o Proprietary Remote Desktop Software
- Work with Headquarters to troubleshoot, install, and maintain network infrastructure
- Active Directory Management; add/delete user accounts, change passwords, assign users to groups
- Setup and maintain network and local printers
- Repair and maintain on-site A/V equipment

March 2012 - February 2014

IT Specialist

STS Aviation Group

- Excelling in a fast paced IT environment working with end users, upper level management, and suppliers, to assist in the overall objective of the department
- Take phone calls from users, troubleshoot computer issues over the phone
- Document calls using Labtech Ticketing System
- Closed 1600+ support tickets in the past year
- Support Smartphones/iPhones



- Setup new Verizon lines and order cell phones and accessories
- o Manage and maintain suspended lines and unused Verizon cell phones
- Setup international plans for users on overseas business trips
- Support Multiple Operating Systems
 - Microsoft Windows 8.1
 - Microsoft Windows 7
 - Microsoft Windows XP
- Support Microsoft Office Suites 2007/2010
 - o Word
 - Excel
 - PowerPoint
 - Access
- Support multiple VOIP phone systems
 - Manufacturers; Digium, Fonality
 - o Order, configure, and install new VOIP desk phones
 - Administer VOIP user accounts (Add, Delete, User Training)
- Remote Desktop Support
 - VNC
 - o UltraVNC
 - LabVNC (Labtech Software)
 - o www.join.me
- Coordinate warranty support/replacement with hardware vendors
- Order, prep, and ship Dell Laptops, Desktops, and Tablets, plus other essential peripheral devices to users in the field
- Image computers using Clonezilla
- Microsoft Server 2007/2010 Administration
 - Account and Profile Creation
 - Password Resets
 - File Restoration
 - Distribution List Creation/Management
 - Security Group Administration
- Join computers to domain
- Assist customers with mapping network drives
- Local account creation for non-domain accounts
- Perform Microsoft Exchange account administration (adding, removing, password changes, etc.) on the Exchange Server environment
- Update inventory database using the Labtech System

Additional Experience:

- March 2012 February 2014, IT Specialist, STS Aviation Group
- June 2003 September 2006, Florida Department of Children and Families, Eligibility Specialist II

